Let's say I've settled on a bunch of metrics.
已经解决了大量的指标
How do I actually make a recommendation?
我应该如何给出建议？
>> So especially when you have multiple metrics, it can be a little bit
尤其是当你有多个指标时 会有一点复杂
tricky because you have multiple comparisons or things along those lines.
因为你有多重比较或者整个过程中的事物
Now what you're really hoping for
现在 你真正希望地是
is that related metrics are all going to move in the same direction.
相关的指标会向同一个方向移动
For example, if you're measuring both click-through rate and
例如 如果你在测试点击率和点击概率
click-through probability, hopefully they'll move in the same direction.
它们会向同一个方向运行
Another thing might happen when you have a composite metric for example.
另一件可能发生的事 如果你有一个组合指标 例如 RPM
RPM which is revenue per thousand queries.
每一千个疑问的营业额
Is composed of both click through rate.
由点击率和每次点击的成本组成
As well as cost per clicks and so if you see.
如果你看见
RPM of them one direction.
它们的 RPM 是一个方向
Hopefully you can look at click through rate in cost per click to understand
你可以看点击率的成本
why it moved in that direction.
每次点击了解为什么向一个方向移动
Now that said, multiple metrics can be unruly.
尽管如此 多个指标是难以控制的
Let's say you've decided that reading time on the page or
比如说 你在页面决定了阅读时间或者
stay time is a good signal.
停留时间是一个很好的信号
People like your page.
人们喜欢你的页面
But clicks are also a good signal.
但是点击也是一个很好的信号
And so then you might see that when you make a UI change to the page
当你在网页上对用户界面做了调整
people spend less time reading, but more time clicking.
你可能会看见人们花更少的时间阅读 但是点击的次数更多了
And then you really have to understand how people are reacting to the change
你真的需要了解人们对改变的反应如何
because you can't quantitatively evaluate which one is better.
因为你无法从数量上评估哪一个更好
That makes sense.
这很重要
I'm guessing that's why sometimes people want to single overall
我在想为什么人们有时想要挑选总的评估标准
evaluation criteria, so they can make the decision based on that?
然后基于这些标准做决定
>> That's right.
是的
I think the main question when you try and come up with an OEC, or
当你尝试和想出 OEC 时 或者总的评估标准 我认为
an overall evaluation criteria, is how do you find a good one?
最主要的问题是你如何找到一个好的？
You really need to understand what your company is doing and
你真的需要了解你的公司在做什么
what the problems are in order to try and come up with saying.
问题是什么 为了尝试和想出 比如说
Ok well how do I balance for
我应该如何平衡
example state time and clicks is it seventy percent and thirty percent.
例如国家时间和点击次数 分布是 70% 和 30% 吗
Is it twenty five and seventy-five.
是 25 和 75
Who knows or maybe.
谁知道呢
Quite frankly.
坦白说
Clicks is a bad measure for.
点击是个糟糕的衡量方式
User experience.
对用户体验来说
On your web site all together.
在你所有的网站上
Right you really have to understand.
你需要了解
The thing about an OEC is that it doesn't absolve you of understanding why
OEC 不会帮你了解为什么
stay time and clicks are moving in these different directions.
停留时间和点击次数以不同的方向移动
What it can be helpful with this balancing long term
使用这个来平衡长期投资有什么好处
investment like return visits to the site
比如短时间内再次访问网站的日常指标
with short term day to day metrics like increased clicks.
比如增加点击量
You don't want to lose one in pursuing the other one.
你不希望在追求另一个的时候丢了这个
And so often the best OICs give you a good balance between those two things.
通常最好的 OIC 让你很好地平衡这两样
>> Okay. And how do you come up with one?
如何想出第一个？
>> Well typically there's a lot of validation in the process but
通常在过程中有许多需要确认
they usually start with some kind of business analysis right so
但是他们经常从一些商业分析开始
you might >> Our company, as a whole,
— 你可能是对的 — 我们公司整体上
wants to look at 25% revenue plus 75% increase usage of the site.
希望达到 25% 的营业额 网站使用量增加 75%
So usually you start from there.
所以从这里开始
And once you have a couple of candidates,
一旦你有许多备选的
you want to actually run a whole bunch of different experiments.
你希望进行许多不同的实验
And validate how they steer you.
确认它们是怎么引导你的
You know, are they steering you in the right direction.
你知道 它们在把你引向正确的方向吗
Now the downside is you want to make sure that you don't plan so much around
缺点是 你想确定并没有计划太多关于
what the company thinks should happen with those experiments that you steer
公司的想法应该与这些实验是一致的
yourself in a way that you hide other changes that you weren't expecting.
你隐藏其他意料之外的变化来引导自己
>> At Google we didn't up doing a little bit.
在 Google 我们的做法
Bit differently.
有所不同
We actually took hundreds of experiments that we had already run and
事实上 我们利用数百个做过的实验
we had made launch decisions about.
我们做出了投放决定
And we got all of the decision makers into a room and
我们让所有决策者进入一个房间
we gave them all of those experiment results.
我们把所有这些实验的结果交给他们
We didn't tell them what the experiment was testing.
我们没有告诉他们这个实验在测试什么
And we didn't give them the actual launch decision.
也没有给他们实际的投放决定
And we made them re-decide based solely on the experiment results
我们让他们根据实验结果重新做决定
whether they would launch change or not.
是否推出变化
From there we could say ok well.
到这里 我们可以说很好
How much did each of you agree with each other and
每个人彼此认同的程度如何
how did you agree with the actual launch decision, and
你有多同意实际的投放决定
using that we actually re-derived the weights for an OAC.
我们用那个重新衡量 OAC 的重要性
Now for us, we came up with an OAC that way, but whenever we tried using
现在对我们来说 我们用那种方式想出一个 OAC
it to make a launch decision everyone sort of look at the OAC and
但是 无论我们何时用它制定投放决策 每个人都看 OAC 然后喜欢
then be like, what were the individual metrics that actually changed.
事实上发生改变的单个指标是什么
So we never actually ended up using the OIC to actually make a decision.
所以 我们实际上从来没有放弃使用 OIC 来制定决策
Now what the sort of tells us is that
现在 告诉我们 OIC
having an OIC doesn't have to be a formal number.
不一定是一个具体的数字
It's really just trying to encapsulate what your company cares about.
只是试着概述你们公司的关注
And how much you're going to be balancing something like stay time
你有多想平衡
and clicks.
停留时间和点击率等